hello my name is grian and today i'm
digging a hole that's right we're making
our way towards area 77 but i am very
quickly running out of dirt because this
hippie tunnel the the tunnel that is
going to
get into area 77
well i've been doing it properly and
that means actually turning the whole
thing into
actual dirt so it looks like a really
cool tunnel look at this so i've got a
nice rail that goes all the way through
and i'm slowly making my way towards
area 77 we are actually officially over
the boundary so this is a pretty big
deal maui
do you want to do this video this is why
you can't have cats in your recording
room well i've actually run out of dirt
so this is as far as the tunnel is going
to go today so let's make our way back
to
hermit land because we've got a lot of
things that we need to do today
what the heck
i i just got off the minecart and it's
put me in this room
i'm guessing i'm below ground
that was really weird let's get out of
here because i'm not gonna be a hippie
for very long there's some big news on
the server and i am going to take
advantage which is why we're going to do
a mid-air
change of skin you ready let's go
[Laughter]
okay as you can see i have turned into
door-to-door salesman green and you'll
see why in a minute i just need to get
back to my base
here we are we need to pop into my base
because that's where these things have
been sitting
you might remember
ages ago months ago i made the did you
die box did you die and i even upgraded
them to have super op armor which you
can no longer get by the way
and
i'm actually going to use the
opportunity of two new hermits that have
joined the server to try and sell them
so let's take these two shulker boxes
and take them all the way back for a
special delivery
to the new guys houses on hermitcraft
now i'm not entirely sure where they've
set up base but i did see a brand new
building pop up over on this side of
area 70s oh my goodness there's so many
planes everywhere yeah this house here
this is what i suspect is one of the new
guys house
although that also looks like a house
that someone set up
and maybe yeah and this one too okay
this might be uh
new hermitville i'm not sure this is uh
obviously a minecraft village and all
the villagers have gone as they usually
do what we're going to do is find the
front door now i am a door to door
salesman so i am going to actually have
to put this in front of a door and hope
that they notice so i put that there
fence post here but most importantly i
actually need to rename these because
these aren't did you die they are did
you
join
hermitcraft
did you join hermitcraft season six i
can't fit the season six in there but
yeah i get you get the point there we go
so if i pop one here
did you join hermitcraft box for sale
three stacks of diamond i couldn't put
the s on there either right so now i
just need a box for them to pay in
this is what we call
targeted advertising this is
door-to-door salesman
in fact i'm gonna make it a double door
and they can't miss it there we go so
that is one of the boxes done outside of
whoever's house this is and then we just
need to do one more these are actually
my last two did you die boxes so if i
get the sales on these that's a pretty
big deal
this place is not safe
this place is really not safe
oh my goodness look at this look at this
field
oh no
i don't like
this oh my goodness
burn
okay so now we need to do one more so
this is the front door of this building
and then if we just pop that there
add the did you join hermitcraft box
there we go
so that is all set up door-to-door
literally door-to-door sales of the did
you join hermitcraft boxes if i can get
those sales that will be all of them
sold and i never have to make them again
they took me hours and hours to produce
and they were quite difficult to sell
but if those two go
that is brilliant news for me but i do
need to make a backup box for myself
which is um always a good idea i've not
been very unlucky i've had most of these
things for a really long time
but you never know when disaster can
strike
but now i need to turn back into a
hippie because
i know that my storage problems are
forever getting out of hand look at all
these but this is for a reason i have
actually produced
one of the the most expensive shulker
boxes there is because we're going to be
starting a redstone project i know we
just got a redstone hippie but impulse
is going to be working on a big display
whereas i'm going to be working on a new
farm
i i've had this really cool idea that i
have to do and i'm probably going to
need impulse's help so that's why he's
here as well but i want to give this a
go myself and see if i can make it but
first i gotta get out of these
salesman's clothes i need i i need to be
a hippie again
i'm back in my hippie skin and something
strange is going on on the server right
now so there's mumbo jumbo online iskall
ren and corrales but every now and again
a message appears in the chat now what
it did say was mumbo jumbo has been
slain by do you want a membership now
message me and that's his advertising
for um at sahara now but what happened
was i got my cam account on and i went
to go and see what mumbo was doing
and this is what i saw
i saw look there it is mumbo was slain
by trespassing in area 77. and this is
what i saw i saw i saw doc
sneaking up to him
being very very sneaky with a name tag
in his hand and i knew exactly what was
going on there he was renaming the
zombie to something else to spoil his
sahara now
advertising campaign and look mumbo
jumbo is now been slain by trespassing
in area 77
well that's just not on is it well this
is a friendly competition so
we're going to go and help mumbo jumbo
out i've got my name tag we're going to
go and sneak in and replace the name of
this zombie asap pronto because we need
to sell some sahara now memberships what
matters
is how we sell them
so this is going to be really good
so mumbo jumbo is all the way back at
his base it feels like the beginning of
the season
we're going into mumbo jumbo's base
to do a little prank how exciting
there we go i love his little banner
here it's like a little mumbo suit it's
so cute okay
now
i don't know if he's actually gonna be
looking but we're here to help that's
that's what we're here to do he didn't
notice doc there so i think it will be
safe oh if i didn't let him know
right i think i just saw his name tag
there it is
oh he's totally moving around
oh
mambo
how do i get down there
he's definitely back from being afk
do i go in this system
we're gonna sneak in the traditional way
oh he just got slain by the zombie again
maybe he's not moving around
oh there we go i've broken in
i just heard him enter some i just heard
him
no skeleton don't give me away
ow that if if i wasn't giving away
already that has that's done it just
keep quiet
just keep quiet i'm scared
i haven't even renamed this name tag i'm
not prepared at all
oh my goodness
no don't
don't
don't do it
oh my goodness he's so close
i'm in a bit of a predicament here i
can't move or do anything
without giving myself away
oh my heart my heart my little heart i
think we've just got to play the long
game i've been waiting like five minutes
here now
i just need to i need to wait this out
oh no no
is he looking for me
he's quite far away now
okay i'm gonna go for it all right let's
make our move to the zombie there we go
there's his little zombie hideout i
think it's safe
unless he's just crouching i don't know
if he's looking for me or not ah the
zombie's gone the zombie is gone well
this infiltration was all for nothing
back to hippie land
i have got the name tag ready check the
blimp in hermitland that's all we need
that was my plan all along but it's been
slightly ruined
boom
[Music]
[Laughter]
i've been thoroughly rumbled there's no
escape for this
there's no escaping this one
i'm thoroughly messed up okay time to
leave time to leave
time to leave you saw nothing
i was only trying to help that really
backfired
really really backfired all hope is not
lost he's getting a new zombie
we're just gonna have to do it a little
bit later on when mumbo's back afk don't
you worry this is not over but we do
need to go back to hippie land
okay we're back in hippie town for now
until mumbo sorts himself out with a new
zombie and then he doesn't even know he
thinks i was just doing the right thing
and changing it back to what it was no
i'm gonna i'm gonna try and plug my own
advert with check the blimp in hermit
land but we're gonna have to save that
for later i've got a lot of redstone
machinery to make as you can see i've
got these shulker boxes ready now what
we're going to do is actually something
i think is quite clever
so i think i'm going to make this little
area over here this i don't know how
much space i'm gonna need i'm not very
good at redstone but this should do it
all of this will be fine and if i need
to move this back i can do but that's
gonna be a nightmare anyway the best way
to explain what i'm going to be doing
with my redstone project which is
probably going to take a couple of
episodes
because i'm quite slow at redstone at
the best of times but i'm going to do my
best to explain with a nice diagram
okay this might look a little bit
confusing at first but this machine is
is a little bit complex but it will be
worth it in the long run this is going
to produce many things and it's going to
be self-sufficient so it all starts with
these three at the top these are all
zero tick farms for plant life we've got
sugar cane bamboo and cactus
the cactus farm links up to two things
the composter which is going to produce
some bone meal and it links up to the
furnace system so i get out of this
some cactus green or green dye and then
i also get some bone meal the bamboo
feeds into the furnace system so does
the cactus that gives me xp and green
dye the cactus also feeds into the
composter which gives us bone meal the
sugar cane farm will obviously give us
sugar cane but the sugar cane will also
feed into the compost you're just going
to have to imagine that i've i've linked
those up because that's confusing
now you know what i'm going to do this
this this diagram is actually working
out quite well it just looks a little
bit complicated but it makes me feel
more clever than i really am there we go
so this is going to go into there
right so basically these three feed the
whole system we're going to get some xp
and green dye sugar cane and some bone
meal the bone meal from the composter is
going to feed the flour farm which is
going to feed me dies
all of these things all of these
machines will work in harmony together
to produce all of these things
which are very very useful and then in
the end we can sell them via the hippie
market so this is going to be an awesome
redstone project even if it did take me
like 10 minutes to understand this whole
diagram thing hopefully it makes sense
right so the first thing we need to do
is make a zero tick sugar cane farm a
zero tick bamboo farm and a zero tick
cactus farm in a way that allows us to
feed it
into other machines so i probably want
to build them slightly in the air anyway
let's take down this mess and get
started
so i'm actually going to be following
someone's tutorial from youtube and his
name is illmango and he makes along with
some of his friends on a different
server to hermitcraft called scicraft
they make these awesome massive
minecraft machines now the one i'm going
to be making is called a zero tick farm
now you don't really need to know what
that means i'm not sure even i quite
understand what it means but essentially
it's just a farm that makes something
really really fast without much lag and
that's the main thing so i went ahead
followed this tutorial and this is the
result a long and rather complex looking
machine but the main thing is does it
work
i have successfully recreated the 16 000
sugarcane zero tick farm i hope i
absolutely hope i was actually surprised
at the the simplicity of it well it's
not simple at all but like i i was able
to follow the tutorial very well it's a
very very good tutorial so well done ill
mango
however i don't know if it actually
works i'm a little bit scared i think
i've done it right
we'll find out when i hit this lever
three two one
that looks right
yes
yes yes yes
okay well uh it might might be working
except that's not actually pushing the
slime at the moment what have i done
wrong i i think i would have been amazed
if it worked first time i'm gonna have
to figure out what i've done wrong oh
i'm totally missing i don't even need to
do any troubleshooting because
that is supposed to be there
i think
because otherwise how is this even
powered i'm going to assume that there
is a delay
and then we can try this again
oh i really should have double checked
with ill mango's video but let's do it
off we go again
yes
this is magic
magic instant sugarcane bush instant
sugarcane
bush
this is brilliant
now i can see why people make these
machines
sugarcane
yes
okay i guess you just leave this running
look at that look how much sugarcane
we're getting
brilliant this is gonna be absolutely
fantastic but this is only one
out of the three machines that we're
going to need and since that only took a
little while i will be able to make the
other two fairly quickly because i think
this is probably one of the bigger ones
out of the three so that is really
really cool
man this is exciting however in the chat
you can see mumbo jumbo was slain by
once sahara now membership message dot
me
he's still going he's still spamming the
chat and he's still online i've got my
i've got my name tag i know how to get
in there let's go and do what we set out
to do first time before we got
thoroughly thoroughly rumbled
there we go he's off again slain by want
sahara now membership message me so he
just back his idea is to spam the chat
my idea is the giant balloon
this time i'm gonna make sure that i
don't give myself away the second i get
through his portal
all right
we're in
he's in the same place as before
let's do this
carefully
this probably wasn't the best way to get
in i can hear him getting hurt
okay we're in
easy does it
we don't want to give ourselves away
obviously we're breaking quite a lot of
blocks there's my tunnel from before
okay just one block
there he is
boom check the blip in hermit land and
we're out
and we're out
yes
and now we get away
mission successful we weren't rumbled
he has no idea
that was so worth it
so worth it and now we scarpa back
because we've got more redstone work to
do mumbos mumbo's sahara now membership
scheme only really works for the people
online
so now that's going to get spammed
people are going to be redirected to my
blimp for the saharan now membership
at least it's got nothing to do with
area 77 this is what happens when mumbo
goes afk
i take your zombie name away
we're back at making these redstone
machineries so this one is now done i
think i'm going to work on the cactus
one and then the bamboo one because i
think they're actually pretty similar
and yeah this is going to be really cool
and then i just need to start linking
these up it's going to take me i think a
couple of episodes to do this because
this is like quite a big project to do
but i think i can get at least these
three machines done in this episode so
let's crack on with it one more time
so we're on to our second machine which
is going to be the zero tick cactus farm
and basically it's kind of like the one
we made over there just a slightly
different design now this one i actually
had a lot more trouble following because
apparently you have to make it pointing
north and that confused me a little bit
i yeah i messed up a couple of times but
overall i think i got it down and these
farms are just absolutely nuts i was
thinking to myself when building this
how did they come up with this this is
this is absolutely insane and after a
little while i managed to make it
now that is machine two out of three
it's amazing how professional i look
having built look at all this look how
look how complicated this looks i i i
made this i didn't design it but i i
built it and
this one i think will work first time
oh my goodness
ill mango you're a genius and everyone
on the science craft server that is
involved in making these you guys are
awesome i would have never come up with
this
machine of lag and flashy it's not laggy
until it's just loud
oh that's that's better but look at this
i'll be honest with it each and every
one of you i have no idea how this one
works i honestly haven't got a clue it's
producing so many characters it's
something to do with these pistons
moving so fast
and they're updating they're like making
oh no okay i'm gonna try and explain
it's something to do with tick speed on
the server i
magic that's what this is this is a
magic box and those are magic cactus
that's i think that's that's the most
scientific
explanation i can come up with and the
scicraft server is actually just a
server full of witchcraft so yeah i
think what we've got here is a magic box
that is successfully producing first
time
a bunch of cactus wow that's a lot of
cactus straight away so this is
the second machine that has been
complete now i'm going to turn this off
so eventually all of these will be
linked up to one big button which i get
to press at the end of all this and it
should all work on its own
either way that's more than enough
redstone for me for today i will
continue this i wish i'd made this
this machine a little higher up so it
was all in line kind of messed that up
but either way
i have done it and it looks awesome so
we got sugarcane we got cactus and all
of that will come together
eventually but it's actually been a few
days since i built my giant blimp and i
want to see if we have any sales for
sahara now membership
let's take a look inside
let's see if the the giant red arrow
worked
oh yes
oh absolutely yes
we've made three stacks of diamonds
not over three stacks of diamonds 100
200 diamonds that means we've sold two
memberships from our blimp i don't know
who they were
but that is absolutely amazing thank you
to those who used my blimp it must have
worked they must have been able to see
these offers inside here
and
oh do we have do we have another
customer
i'll uh i'll uh i'll leave you to it
and speaking of the new hermits that is
corrales there one of the hermits that
has rejoined the server
i went and put a did you join
hermitcraft oh i've only got four
rockets what's this gal doing here oh oh
ow
no that was bad timing
that is like the most your friend turns
up and your elytra breaks and you fall
in lava you can't make that up so what
i've done is my door-to-door salesman
thing and i have done the uh they've
opened the door did you join her craft
oh
yes
yes yes yes
oh my goodness look at all these
diamonds
okay so we sold
one did you join hermitcraft box to
whoever lives here
and i did another door-to-door sales
all the way over here at whoever lives
at this house
did they also take the box
ah no
oh
but they've totally paid that's amazing
i'm actually to leave these in here just
in case because they haven't taken the
box yet but i'm going to assume those
diamonds are mine so that's one two
three four five six seven eight nine
nine
stacks of diamonds in one episode
that is really really good obviously
those 200 diamonds are going in the
sahara vault
but that is a really really good start
and i think
on that note as i glide back to hippie
land
that is all for this episode thank you
very much for watching it has been
eventful we have made some redstone
machines we have pranked mumbo jumbo our
favorite pastime of course
and we've made a bunch of diamonds thank
you very much for watching everyone and
good bye